MkvDrama.net
It's now or never.
Drake Palma!
You're my boyfriend now!
I'm Alys.
Alys Zyril Perez, soon to be Palma!
Hello!
You’re my girlfriend.
Act like one.
Those girls are annoying.
What about me? Am I not annoying?
You're annoying.
And that’s fine.
Dream on. You're ugly.
You're not handsome.
I know.
I don't wanna be handsome.
I just want to be loved.
By you, perhaps.
Tss.
Birdbrain.
You're too much!
Noob!
My noob!
I'm territorial.
You told me that you
don't like me anymore.
So, I'm trying to forget you.
But why are you making it
so damn impossible?
I don’t —
Shut up!
- Seulement vous.
I love you, Alys Zyril Perez.
I love you so much too,
Drake Sebastian Palma.
Yes. I just landed, Silly.
How are you?
I told you, I'm fine.
It will be fine.
Don't worry about me.
Where are you, anyway?
I'm about to head out.
But I'm not coming home yet.
Because I need to pass by
the shop to meet a client.
You're making a big step, Zy.
And I know you’ll be fine.
You always are.
Thanks. So where are you headed now?
I'm about to leave the airport.
I'm here.
Hurry up, I've been waiting since earlier.
I'm almost there.
I'm so excited to see you.
Me too.
Alys Zyril Perez?
Yes?
Uh, I think it's the jetlag.
We can do this later
once you’re fully awake.
No, it's okay. I'm okay.
Good.
So, this will be your room.
Oh, Kei's not around.
Uhm...who’s Kei?
Oh, your parents specifically
requested for you
to be roommates with the
smartest kid in this building.
Gosh, Mom is so mean.
But I guess this is okay, too.
But at least someone will
help me with my assignments.
Uhm, anyway...
This is the list of your
books and your schedule.
I just arrived in New York and
I'm greeted with a schedule immediately?!
And advertising looks difficult.
Why did you even choose this, mommy?
I think I'm about to die.
And here are your keys.
All your things are here already
so I guess I'll leave you to it.
Good luck!
Thank you, Ms. Rachel.
See you around!
It's only the two of us here.
Is this Kei a good person?
St. Collete, I don't want
an awful roommate.
I hope Kei is a good girl.
Maybe she has the same attitude
as my former schoolmate at SCA.
St. Collete, I hope not.
Thank you!
Hi, Drakey Baby!
I miss you so much already
even though I haven't been away
from the Philippines for a week yet.
Why are you calling
at this time of the day?
Aren't you supposed to
be sleeping or something?
Come on!
You're the one I missed,
and yet you're the one who's mad.
I'm not mad.
I'm just concerned about your welfare.
I know it's 5 AM there
because it's 5 PM here.
But I just can't settle down here.
I have no one to talk to.
Then talk to people.
That's what you're good at.
Huh?
You annoy most people,
so they become forced to talk to you.
That's what you did
the first time I met you.
You annoyed me.
You're really too much, Drake!
You're still so mean to me!
I thought you'd be nicer to me
since you said I love you already.
But you're still such a meanie.
Noob.
Hmm?
I can see your premature boobs from here.
Eww! You're such a pervy now, Drake!
That’s so indecent!
What could I do?
You tempt me so much.
You’re unbelievable!
So, how are you coping up?
I don't like it here.
There are so many blondes.
And they're all so tall.
And most of all,
all of them are English speaking here.
Like, straight-up English.
Go on, laugh!
You know, you're so mean to me.
Ever since I left, it's like...
You keep making fun of me!
You don't love me anymore, do you?
Stupid.
Of course, I love you.
I always wear this even if it looks weird.
It's not! That's so cute, you know.
Whatever.
Anyway, did you already meet your roommate?
Not yet. But Kei's her name.
OMG! Whichever Kei this is,
I hope she's not bitchy like Kei Chu.
Be nice.
You'll be with her for quite some time.
Even if you're stupid in English,
try to talk anyway.
They won't notice your grammar.
‘Cause they're using
wrong grammar, as well.
Really?
I'll go now.
- I need to help my Dad tomorrow.
- Oh!
- Bye.
- You’re going back to sleep?
Isn't it morning already?
Don't sleep anymore, let's just talk.
Miss me that much, noob?
Good night.
I love you.
I still get giddy every time
Drake says I love you to me.
Back then, all he would say was “Tss”.
At least there's a variety now.
There's I love you and I miss you now.
See? My boyfriend is improving!
Hey.
I said I love you, where's my reply?
Fine.
I love you, too.
Bye.
I told Alys I’m leaving for US
to pursue another course.
But that's not the whole truth.
The truth is I left because...
I want to forget her.
But why am I still
thinking about you, Alys?
Tripp, you can do this.
Baby steps.
You'll get there.
You need to get through this.
Dad, why did you bring Tofer
here in New York?
Unbelievable!
You allowed me to go to New York.
But with this nuisance.
Tripp, that is your cousin.
And it's better for you to have company.
Makes it easier to move.
It's just so not cool, Dad.
If Drake is annoying,
I’m way more annoyed at this nobody.
You don’t know,
but he’s such a bad influence.
Goodness, Tripp.
Learn to live with him.
Bond with each other and get close to him.
Oh!
Tripp!
You'll get wrinkles faster like that!
You should just relax, cousin!
Just be happy, you know!
My god.
Dad, he just got here.
And there's all kinds of mess already.
His trash is everywhere.
This bastard is making me a slave.
I am pretty sure you'll
get used to him soon.
Ouch, that hurts, Tripp.
You only used to be like this
with Drake before.
Why are you like this with me now, too?
So hurtful. You're mean now?
Okay, I have to go.
Hope your decision to go to New York
is good for you and our business.
Hello? Hello, Dad?
Hello?! Hey!
Look, he hung up!
You're so hotheaded.
You're just supposed to relax, bro.
Relax.
Oh! Where are you going?
To eat.
You coming?
Yeah! Where are we gonna eat?
You have so many questions.
I said we're eating out.
There's diner there.
It’s fine, as long as it’s food.
Are you coming or not?
Yes, okay!
You’re such a PMS.
You're acting like Drake.
One more word about Drake.
Mention him one more time.
I'm making you sleep outside.
Let you freeze to death.
Take it easy!
You can’t take a joke.
Oh, oh, wait!
I’m going with you!
Aish! Kent!
You’re being too clingy!
Ever since CB and I became classmates,
you've been super duper clingy!
Argh! It’s gross!
Come on, Bee!
Please come to my house for dinner.
I don’t want to!
You might introduce me to your parents.
That's right.
That's why I'm inviting you, right?
I don't want it even more!
I'm not prepared for meet the parents.
You're too much, Bee!
You know, we've been together
for almost six months.
And so?
What do you mean? Come on, Bee!
Say yes already, please!
Come to my house with me.
You can go with me.
Aish! Come on, Kent!
Can we just do this
next time instead? Okay?
I don’t understand you, Aya!
Other girls want to be introduced
to their boyfriend's parents.
But you, you don’t want to?
Whatever!
Stay with that Sheen of yours!
Bee!
- Ugh!
- Bee!
Okay. Say cheese!
Cheese.
Hold on.
Drake...
Fix your smile.
You look like you're smiling at a funeral.
I told you it's for a pictorial.
This is how I smile.
If you don't like,
I can just go to my room.
Just smile!
Alright!
One more. Say cheese!
Cheese.
Okay. Next is the family.
Drake, smile.
I wonder if my brother would like me.
I think I'll make a really cool brother.
I'm waiting for Ethos already.
I want to meet him already.
But I also want to have my own baby.
But I should wait.
Everybody say cheese!
Cheese!
Come on, Alys, pick up.
Why aren't you picking up?
Did she get into trouble again?
Drake...
That troublemaker —
What?
I know you want to go to New York.
Yes, Dad. Can I go now?
Come on, Dad. This isn't fair.
I've been following you around.
I agreed to this photoshoot.
I even agreed to wear this shirt.
I even agreed to sign those damned papers
saying that I won't get my inheritance
if I take my studies for granted.
I've been practically
licking your ass, Dad.
Calm down, son.
I have a deal for you.
What now?
Take your APE.
If you pass and finish it,
I’ll allow you to take a vacation.
But your vacation's only for a week.
Easy. Prepare my tickets now, Dad.
Is that for real?
I'm a genius, Dad.
I thought you knew that already.
I'll go now. I need to study.
What to do now, Alys?
St. Collete, pray for me.
I don't even like my advertising course.
And why is it even in New York?
I'm so far from my comfort zone.
And I'm also LDR with Drake.
But maybe I do need this.
What even is four years?
Hmp!
I'll prove to mommy and
myself that I can do this!
You can do this, Alys! Let's go!
I miss you, Alys.
I miss you already.
But I think this has to happen.
For now, I will do my best here.
Get myself a good career.
So I can build a family with you.
And yes, I’ll visit you soon.
I miss you badly, my Noob.
How can I move on from you, Alys?
You're so difficult to forget.
Maybe since I'm so far from you,
it'll be easier.
I'll just focus on myself first.
Good morning, New York!
This is your morning weather update
from a city that never sleeps!
We’ve got cold temperatures to
kick things off this morning.
Plenty of fresh spring air,
across the city.
Alys!
Wake up!
What the heck is wrong with you?!
Kei?
Get up!
Kei, is that you?
Look!
Alys Zyril Perez.
Are you even listening to me?
Why?
What is it?
What?
Should I just toss these plates?
Oh, sorry.
Sorry, Kei.
I don't know how to wash the dishes.
How do I do it?
God! You're hopeless!
Why are you even here?
To study?
Are you kidding me?
You, Alys Zyril Perez?
The lowest in our batch?
You're too much, Kei!
My grades were high last semester!
OMG. Kei is super pretty now!
Huhu, I want to be like that, too!
What?!
I'm sorry, Kei.
I'll just buy disposables.
Whatever!
Kei?
What?
What's your course?
First, Alys.
The term course refers to the subject.
The proper question is,
what is your degree program?
Oh, so that's how it is.
So, what's your degree program?
Advertising. I started last semester.
Oh! Same!
I'm advertising, too!
But it's just my first sem.
Do you have nothing better to do?
Kei, it's too early for you to study.
Let's go jogging at Central Park.
In this weather?
No, thank you.
Okay.
Super short-tempered.
Tripp! Come on! Wake up!
Wake up! Let's go!
Let's go walk around NYCU!
Tripp, come on! Let's go!
Come with me!
My god.
Just go to your mom's house!
You have a house!
Yet you want to take up space here.
Come on! Come on, please!
Let’s go, come on! Come with me!
- Come with me!
- Stop it!
I said I don't want to!
Leave by yourself!
I just want to sleep.
Don't you understand?
What’s wrong with you?
Tss!
What's his problem?
And he has the nerve to get angry.
Meanwhile, my class will start in a day.
Feeling nervous.
I don’t know anyone here.
I have no friends.
The people at NYCU are smart.
That's why I need to do my best.
I have to study hard.
So that when I go back to the Philippines,
I’ll be better than Drake.
That's all I really want, anyway.
Because Zyril is already with him.
Goodness, Tripp.
When will this end?
Good morning, New York!
Good morning, Rachel!
Good morning, Ms. Perez!
Good morning!
Hi, Drakey Baby!
Tss. Missed me?
Of course!
Did you miss me, too?
I don't know.
I'm liking this set up, actually.
Huh?
But why?
Don't you want to see me?
Good morning!
Yes.
Because I'm tempted when I'm near you.
Goodness, Drake Sebastian Palma!
Are you really only after my body?
Joke!
Look at this guy.
Ever since I left,
he's been laughing all the time.
I think I'm really turning into a comedian.
I've just been busy.
I've been with my dad all day.
How have you been?
Just out on a jog.
This is actually tiring.
Stupid.
Of course!
Did you meet your roommate already?
Yes, it's Kei Chui!
Amazing, right?
The world's so small!
Did it surprise you?
I got surprised, too.
Hello, Drake?
Are you still there?
Yes.
What were you saying?
Nothing.
I said my roommate is Kei Chui.
Kei seems good.
You should befriend her.
You think so?
Drake?
Hmm?
Can you go on a vacation here?
Even just for a week.
Please?
Drake!
I said I'll visit you on Thanksgiving.
Can't wait?
No! Because —
Huh?
What happened?
Why did it disappear?
Will Drake and I work out?
I mean, they say LDR is hard, right?
Ugh, annoying!
Gosh! It really won’t work —
Come on!
What the hell?!
She’s in a bad mood.
Zy?
How so?
She’s supposed to be in the Philippines.
What would she be doing here?
She is really crazy about my cousin.
Oh man, I really don’t know!
Life is so weird.
Focus, Tripp.
You're here to study.
Let's just go to school.
Hey! Watch it!
Sorry.
Be thankful you're pretty.
I know, right?
I thought she was American?
Life is so weird.
Such a cool new hair color!
Bee, look!
Bee!
Bee, my hair is so beautiful.
Look at it!
Bee.
Kent, come on.
You're sulking too much.
I just didn't attend the dinner.
My reason is valid! I’m scared!
Bee, are you taking summer classes?
I thought we were
visiting bestie in New York?
Bee...
I'm sorry.
You know, Aya.
You're the only girl that lasted
this long with me, right?
I just want to introduce you to my parents.
Why don't you want to?
Because, Kent...
Are you sure?
You’ll introduce me?
I mean, me?
Gabriella Pineda?
Are you serious?
You're going to introduce
me to your parents?
And why should they be scared of you?
Because you look like a gangster?
Or because sometimes you go crazy?
Or because sometimes you
punch people out of nowhere?
They shouldn’t be scared of you, right?
Do you want us not to reach seven months?
I'll break up with you!
Right here, right now!
Huh?
- Ouch!
- You always use that to scare me!
Well, because...
that's the only thing that scares you.
That's because Kent loves Aya very much.
Right?
I don't know with you.
I'll just schedule my flight.
Are you really going?
I really want to go, Bee, but...
I need to attend summer classes.
The subject wasn't offered
to me back in first sem.
I'll fall behind the curriculum
if I don't take it this summer.
Alright.
It looks like I can’t do anything about it.
Just promise me, Bee!
You won't fall for Sheen
while you're there in the U.S.
You know too much, Kent!
Leave me alone!
Bee, promise me!
Stop it!
Stop, you’re talking nonsense!
Stay there.
I'll miss you.
Really?
Mmm.
Me too, I’ll miss you.
Come with us, please?
How was the exam?
It was easy.
When's the result?
I don't know.
But I'm sure I aced it.
Some of the questions,
I've already read it somewhere.
That's why I love reading, Dad.
Your Aunt Katrina's not here.
Come eat with me instead.
Your Uncle Tristan said Tripp and
Tofer are living at his flat.
Tofer?
That annoying guy?
You're so mean to your cousin!
He's so loud and annoying.
Tripp is probably getting
annoyed with him too.
Serves him right for
being there while I'm here.
Alys’ dorm is close there.
Wait, you do know she’s
living in a dorm, right?
It's great that Alys got high grades.
That's why she got in at NYCU.
The papers and essay that
Andy and Dana made are good.
And so?
Nothing, Drake.
I just wanted to tell you.
Even if you’re so smart
and you graduated,
I still want you here in the Philippines.
I don't want us to be apart.
Clingy.
You're disgusting, Dad.
You’re so cute, Drake.
Let’s eat.
We barely even spend time together anymore.
Hey, is someone sitting here?
- Huh?
- Is someone sitting here?
What? I'm sorry?
Is someone sitting here?
- Uh, no one is.
- Okay.
Are you new here?
Uhm...
I'm Karen.
Yeah. I'm Alys Zyril Perez.
Alys Zyril Perez.
Can I call you Zy or Zyril?
Only Tripp calls me Zy or Zyril.
I know he’s here in New York, too.
I wonder how he is.
I hope you're doing alright, Tripp.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Oh, I mean it's nothing.
Uhm, you can just call me Alys.
Alys.
Nice to meet you, Alys.
Nice to meet you too.
Uhm, Karen?
Yeah?
Can I ask for your FB account?
So I can add you and we
can maybe become friends.
You're so cute, Alys!
You know, you're like my little sister.
Yeah, just search me up.
The name's Karen Burmejo.
Burmejo?
Yeah.
By any chance, are you Filipino?
Actually, I am!
- I was actually born in the Philippines,
- I knew it.
but raised here in the States.
How about you?
I was born and raised there.
And now I'm here.
And I badly wanna go back home.
Aww.
You're such a cutie pie. Come here!
Let me give you a hug.
You know what, you got this, girl.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I promise you.
Wait, why are you here?
For work? School? Family drama?
Studies.
I'm currently studying at NYCU
and I'm taking advertising.
Oh my gosh, that's so funny.
I go there too!
But I'm getting my Master's.
Really, sister?
Oh, is it okay if I call you sister?
Sure.
So does that mean you
can teach me sometimes?
Of course, baby girl.
When I'm free,
I'll teach you everything.
You've nothing to worry about.
You know, you really
resemble my little sister.
Then she must be really cute like me.
She's so cute and fluffy!
I wanna die!
Sorry.
You know, I'm really hungry.
Do you wanna get lunch?
Do you like Thai food?
I know this really good place.
- Sure!
- Come on, let's go!
Karen, this is actually
my first time eating in a Thai resto.
- Hey.
- What?
Can someone join your table?
The place is packed.
Uhm, sure. Whatever.
- Oh, thank you.
- Sorry.
It's weird.
Uh...
Uh, so the waiter told me
I can sit here?
Oh, uhm. I have to take this call.
I'll be right back.
Okay!
And you are?
I'm Christofer Ann Palma.
Palma?
I wonder how this
person is related to Drake.
Well, there are lots of Palma in the world.
There are tons of Perez too.
But we're not all related.
Christofer Ann?
Hey! Don't laugh.
Ann is from my grandmother.
I'm her only grandkid so...
Yeah, my name is Ann.
Whatever.
Ann and he’s a guy.
Huh?
Are you Filipino?
You're Filipino too?!
Oh my gosh, fellow countrymen!
I can speak in Tagalog now!
Hey, calm down.
You're so noisy.
Sorry, I can’t help it.
I miss speaking in Tagalog.
You speak Tagalog, as well.
- True.
- You’re using English on me.
Wait.
You didn't shake my hand yet.
What's your name?
Alys Zyril Perez.
Alys Perez?
By any chance,
is Drake your boyfriend?
Oops.
Let me see.
I like what's going on in here.
I think you should add more
to this side so it's not like...
you know, all over the place.
Hi!
Are you Ms. Stinson?
Yes, I am.
Are you Ms. Perez?
Yes, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry, I still have jetlag.
I just got back from New York.
No worries.
So, where's the groom?
Oh, he's on his way.
Sorry, he's just really busy.
I'll show you the list of cake designs
that we have so we can proceed.
- Okay?
- Sure.
Make yourself at home.
Thank you.
Uh, Ms. Perez.
This is my groom, Drake.
Babe, this is Ms. Perez.
She is the one making our cake.
Hi, Alys.
So where are you headed now?
I'm about to leave the airport.
I'm here.
Hurry up, I've been waiting since earlier.
I'm almost there.
I'm so excited to see you.
Me too.
Babe!
- Welcome back!
- Wow!
You brought flowers.
Thank you!
How's Harvard?
It was okay.
Piece of cake.
Paris will be good for you, Zy.
Especially now that you got
the course you wanted.
So I’m sure you’ll ace it.
I'm rooting for you, Zy.
I'm always rooting for you.
Babe!
Ms. Perez!
Yes?
You dropped this.
Oh, geez. Thanks, sir.
Oh my gosh, Alys.
Who was that?
Oh, it's nothing.
I just dropped my passport.
Come on, Zy.
You're so clumsy.
Silly!
I miss you already.
Seriously, when I see you,
I'm going to hug you to death!
I’m sorry, Zy.
There’s nothing I can do.
You left me here.
Now you’ll have to suffer with Tofer.
Wow, thanks so much!
My boyfriend is so kind!
Boyfriend.
That sounds so nice.
Seriously, Marco.
We've been together for two years.
You're still getting
giddy for me until now?
What can I do?
My girlfriend is so pretty.
Shut up!
And because of that,
you're coming home right now!
Please, please!
I can't.
I need to do something here in New York.
I need to close a deal.
Fine.
Do your best there, okay?
I'll call you later when I get to the shop.
Love you!
Alright.
Love you more!
Alright then, your boyfriend still
has something to do.
Okay! Bye, boyfriend!
I love you!
Bye, Zy!
Oh!
Welcome home, Perez!
Why did you even come home too?
Well, of course.
Who'll watch over you?
I don't need a babysitter, Tofer.
I'm already 22 years old.
And plus, I've been living alone
for four years.
Are you freaking kidding me?
Alys...
Well, Tripp thinks differently.
So, are you ready?
Well, do I have a choice?
Goodness, Perez.
On the next episode of
Dating Alys Perez.
Don't you have a crush
on Drake's girlfriend?
You're on your usual
crazy self again.
I'm in love with you again.
You're nuts.
I know!
And I promised your girlfriend that
I'm never gonna flirt with you ever again!
How are you and Kei?
Bestie said they're roommates.
Can you imagine?
Out of everyone Alys could have
as a roommate, it’s Kei Chui!
Tripp!
Alys is nice. Drake is bad.
Congratulations, you passed the test!
Your flight's tomorrow afternoon.
Drake!
They’re not a good match, man!
You and Alys are a better match, you know.
Honestly, I'm a TripLys fan, you know!
MkvDrama.net